[A Good Day to Ascend]
[Episode 3: Nuo Arts]
You lowly ant,
you should feel honored.
Today, you'll witness
something you've never seen in your life—
the orthodox Nuo arts.
Heavenly soul births the White Tiger.
Earthly spirit gives rise
to the Azure Dragon.
Preserve the upper elixir field,
to seize the immortal's panacea.
Xu Ying!
No matter how strong you are,
can you overpower this endless Vine Arts?
Don't think that just because you've
picked up some lowly demonic techniques,
you can challenge the Nuo arts.
Vine Arts!
Who's the loser now?
Strangle!
You're overconfident.
Once entangled by these vines, he's dead.
Should I save him or not?
We barely know each other.
Don't worry.
I will spare your life.
After all,
the Zhou family wants you alive.
But the rest of your parts?
No need for them.
What?
Fire...
You're still alive?
Thanks for the reminder.
No matter how strong you are,
can you overpower this endless Vine Arts?
Vine Arts.
Fire
counters wood.
[Burning wood with fire]
[Great Sun Guiding Technique]
[Elephant Force Bull Fist]
Great Sun Body-Refining.
A flash of insight mid-battle,
and you break my Nuo technique.
If it had been the Zhou family's
true Nuo technique,
I probably wouldn't have broken through.
Looks like even as their dog,
the Zhou family never taught you
their true Nuo arts.
Shut up!
Ant Xu Ying!
My turn now!
You could have been a man,
but you chose to be a dog.
So fast.
You slave!
All your so-called efforts
are just relying on others' power
to bully the weak
and doing the Zhou family's dirty work!
I'll kill you!
Go to hell!
You're just a commoner!
A little power and you put on airs!
You asked for a beating!
Entangle!
Great Prison Lotus!
[Elephant Force Bull Fist]
What...
You monster!
Elephant Force Bull Fist, fourth form!
Bad luck, begone!
Begone!
I need to leave this place
and head into the woods quickly.
Keep chasing.
You'll regret it soon enough.
One solid punch—
that's all it takes to end this.
Oh no.
Such powerful pressure.
I can't move.
Go to hell!
Now's my chance.
Trying to run? Did I allow you to move?
You bullies!
Take this!
I'll remember
what you did to me today.
Damn it.
He got away.
Judicial Officer Ding Quan!
Were you the one casting the Nuo arts?
Have you found the thief Xu Ying?
Ying, if we don't leave now,
it'll be too late.
Let's go.
Yuan Qi,
thank you.
You think I ran away?
You avenged the villagers,
even risking your life to kill a deity.
Among us demons,
loyalty is everything.
You showed honor and justice.
I couldn't just abandon you
and run away alone.
I'm a human,
not a demon.
Don't be so sure.
What if you're not?
I've never heard of a human
mastering demonic techniques this quickly.
Could this be why the Zhou family
wants to capture me alive?
They don't think I'm
half-demon, do they?
No.
I'm definitely a human.
I'm from Xujiaping.
My parents are both from Xujiaping.
Lord Wei Chu,
he's still alive.
Barely hanging on, by the life force
from the first level of Niwan Secret Art.
[Warden
Wei Chu]
Beaten to this state by a country bumpkin.
What a disgrace
to the name of a Nuo Shaman.
Yeah.
Even if we save him,
he'll be good for nothing.
Might as well leave him to die.
Let's hurry and catch that Xu Ying.
No.
As fellow Nuo Shamans
serving the Zhou family,
we should save him.
Thank you for saving my life,
Lord Wei Chu.
Ding,
how did you end up like this?
That Xu Ying practices demonic techniques,
and a snake demon ambushed me from behind.
That's why I'm in such a state.
Rest easy, Ding.
As for capturing Xu Ying,
leave it to me.
Oh no.
The fight was so fierce.
When did you snatch this
from that Nuo Shaman?
When I dislocated his joints.
As expected of an official.
So rich.
Cultivation techniques?
Doesn't look like any
demon techniques I've seen.
Could this be
the Zhou family's secret arts?
The Zhou family would never pass on
their orthodox arts to outer disciples.
Even this simplified Nuo technique
and manual aren't
allowed out of the Zhou household.
This handwritten copy
must have been secretly copied
by Ding Quan from the Zhou family.
Interesting.
What Ding Quan practices
is probably the Niwan Secret Art.
He cultivates it superficially,
yet his strength is already so terrifying.
The real Zhou family arts
must be far more powerful.
But if I can break through to the
sixth level of Elephant Force Bull Fist,
I won't fear Ding Quan.
Yuan Qi,
let me show you the essence
of the Elephant Force Bull Fist.
You watch closely
and refer to the scriptures.
This is the
Great Sun Body-Refining Technique.
It refines the body
and purges impurities.
That's not right.
You're doing it wrong.
Stop looking.
This is the
Great Sun Body-Refining Technique.
I realized this during
my fight with Ding Quan—
it's the missing one between
the Great Sun Guiding Technique
and the Elephant Force Bull Fist.
It wasn't hard to figure out.
Wasn't hard?
Three generations of my family
haven't figured it out,
and you did so fast?
You're lying.
The sixth level
of the Elephant Force Bull Fist...
is mastered.
I give up.
This guy's not human.
Yuan,
the key to practicing
the Elephant Force Bull Fist
lies in qi and blood and body tempering.
When your qi and blood are vigorous enough
and strong enough,
you can move to the next level.
and comprehended
the Great Sun Body-Refining Technique.
It's perfect for you.
Let me try.
It's
coming
from the...
It's coming from
the direction of that broken temple.
[Stone Mountain God
Huang Simping]
Lord Stone Mountain God,
could it be that thief Xu Ying?
I heard Xu Ying just escaped from
God of Mount Hong today
and went into hiding.
I think it's very likely him.
I also heard this afternoon
that county officers
were sneaking around nearby.
They must be looking for Xu Ying too.
Congratulations, Lord Stone Mountain God.
The credit for capturing Xu Ying
will definitely be yours.
Yours.
It's only a merit if we can catch him.
Let's go
and take a look.
I...
I've cultivated the fifth level
of the Elephant Force Bull Fist.
I've achieved divine elephant strength.
Elephant god manifestation!
Over the two or three hundred years,
among three generations of my family,
no snake has cultivated the fourth level
of the Elephant Force Bull Fist.
I didn't expect
now under your guidance,
I've reached the fifth level in no time.
It turns out cultivation is so easy,
so simple.
Congratulations, Niu.
But your breakthrough just now
caused a surge of qi and blood
that made an elephant's cry—
it will surely
alert the nearby Phantom Deities
and the officers chasing us.
We need to leave now.
Right.
If we get trapped in
this temple by pursuers,
we're done for.
What's that sound?
Pursuers?
So fast? And with such a commotion?
It's the Phantom River.
The Phantom River?
There's no such river around Lingling.
It's the Phantom River
of the Phantom Realm.
The Phantom River has changed its course
and crossed into the mortal world.
What are these green threads?
They're ghosts.
So many ghosts are out.
The mortal world is going to suffer.
If his plan is successful,
[Next Episode]
Then the Qi cultivators will rise again.
A few insignificant mortals deaths
are not worth mentioning.
I didn't expect
the first person I saw
when I woke up after 3,000 years was you.
What monster is this?
I'll tear you apart
and tear off your bones one by one!